★制作软件：                           ★
★生肉啃食机:Raw-subtitle-nibble-machine★
★Srt合并盒子:SrtMergeBox              ★
https://github.com/xinghuo4096/Raw-subtitle-nibble-machine
https://github.com/xinghuo4096/SrtMergeBox
-把你的臭屁股从我身边拿开。
- Get your skanky ass away from me.
击打砖块。
Hit the bricks.
容易的
Easy!
愚蠢的婊子。
Dumb bitch.
你好吗？
- How you doin'?
晚上好。
Nice night.
凉爽的微风。
Cool breeze.
伙计，你知道你不必那样对待她。
Man, you know you didn't have to treat her like that.
我的意思是，当然，是的，有时候爱情
可能很残酷，但它是不必要的副产品。
I mean, sure, yeah, sometimes love can be cruel,
我的意思是，当然，是的，有时候爱情
可能很残酷，但它是不必要的副产品。
but it's an unnecessary byproduct.
这他妈的不是重点。
It's not the point of the damn thing.
-我要数到十。
- I'm gonna count to ten.
然后我会把你从沥青路面上弹下来。
Then I'm gonna bounce you off the damn asphalt.
一、二、三…-你是肉食者吗？
One, two, three…
- You a meat eater?
我正在密切关注我的胆固醇。
I'm keeping a close eye on my cholesterol.
我听说食肉动物的血液中有较高的负荷。
I heard carnivores had a higher load in their blood.
-我的血跟什么有关系？
- What the hell does my blood gotta do with anything?
-我只是想看看我吃什么。
- I'm just trying to watch what I eat.
-什么？
- What?
-谢谢大家！
- Thank you, everyone!
谢谢大家，非常感谢。
Thank you, everyone, thank you very much.
你好，俄亥俄州阿克伦！
Hello, Akron, Ohio!
我听不见你说话！
I can't hear you!
我们开始了。
There we go.
今天不仅是你余生的第一天，
Today is not only the first day of the rest of your lives,
也是最好的一天，
but it is the best day, because today,
因为今天，
we are going to learn how to get what you want
我们将学习如何从你的生活中获得你想要的。
out of the life that you are living.
但是如果你不知道它是什么，你
就不能得到你想要的，是吗？
But you can't get what you want
但是如果你不知道它是什么，你
就不能得到你想要的，是吗？
if you don't know what it is, can you?
人群：不，你不能！
Crowd: No, you can't!
-告诉我我想要什么。
- Tell me what I want.
-你想让莎拉也爱你！
- You want Sarah to love you back!
-是的，确实如此。
- Yes, exactly.
但这并不容易。
But it is not easy.
这是一段旅程。
It's a journey.
在我到达目的地之前，
And before I reach my destination,
有一个秘密我必须学习。
there's a secret that I have to learn.
人群：秘密是什么，雷金纳德？
Crowd: What's the secret, Reginald?
-告诉我们！
- Tell us!
如果你总是做你一直做的事，
- If you always do what you've always done,
你就会得到你一直得到的。
you'll always get what you've always got.
如果你总是做你一直做的事，你就会得到你一直得到的。
If you always do
what you've always done,
如果你总是做你一直做的事，你就会得到你一直得到的。
you'll always get what you've always got.
如果你总是做你一直做的事，
If you always do what you've always done,
你就会得到你一直得到的。
you'll always get what you've always got.
-嘿，瑞吉世界。
- Hey, Regi-world.
瑞吉回合。
Regi-round.
Regi wide过来了。
Regi-wide, comin' through.
你知道肥胖羞辱最终会失去它的影响力，
- You know eventually fat-shaming
对吧？
will lose its punch, right?
我太胖了，我有自己的邮政编码。
I'm so fat, I have my own zip code.
我太胖了，我最喜欢的项链是食物链。
I'm so fat that my favorite necklace is the food chain.
我太胖了，
I'm so fat that when I step on the scale,
当我踩到秤上时，
it says "To be continued."
我太胖了，当我去海滩时，绿色
和平组织会出现把我推到海里。
I'm so fat that when I go to the beach,
我太胖了，当我去海滩时，绿色
和平组织会出现把我推到海里。
Greenpeace shows up to shove me in the ocean.
我太胖了…-是的，我知道了。
I'm so fat… - Yeah, I got it.
超级有趣。
Super funny.
我快笑死了，
I'm about to die laughing from how funny you are
因为你对肥胖有多么可笑。
about being obese.
-我太胖了，所以当我…嗨，莎拉嘿，雷金纳德。
- I'm so fat, that when I…
Hi, Sarah.- Hey, Reginald.
从不没有机会。
Never.No chance.
“嗯，不用了，谢谢你，雷金纳德。
"Um, no, thank you, Reginald.
我不喜欢你这样。”
I don't like you like that."
永远
Forever.
-欢迎来到Slushy Shack。我能帮你什么？
- Welcome to Slushy Shack.How can I help you?
-欢迎来到Slushy Sh
ack。我能帮你什么忙吗？
- Welcome to Slushy Shack.How may I help you?
-你不必每次都这么说，你知道。
- You don't have to say that every time, you know.
-疯狂的事情。
- Crazy thing.
-事实上，我…我知道。它在手册中。
- Actually, I… I do.It's in the manual.
-没有手册，我们都知道。
- There is no manual, and we both know it.
我要一杯巧克力风，
I'll get a Chocoholic Blast,
但我想让你在里面加一小撮热带椰子，
but I want you to add just a pinch of Tropical Coconut
但不要太多，
in there with it, but not too much
否则我会有一种奇怪的回味。
or I get a weird aftertaste in my mouth.
-一针见血。-这只是一个表达。
- An exact pinch.- It's just an expression.
但是想象一下，用手指捏一撮泥，把它加
到我的泥里，用勺子把同样的量加进去。
But imagine taking a pinch of slushy with your fingers
但是想象一下，用手指捏一撮泥，把它加
到我的泥里，用勺子把同样的量加进去。
and adding it into my slushy, but use a spoon
但是想象一下，用手指捏一撮泥，把它加
到我的泥里，用勺子把同样的量加进去。
to add the same amount instead.
-明白了。马上，克莱尔。
- Got it.Right away, Claire.
明天晚上见，
- See you tomorrow night,
一如既往。
like always.
-“牵牛花，故事是什么？”
- "What's the Story, Morning Glory?"
-绿洲，很好。
- Oasis, nice.
-“故事是什么”…-“工作婊子”布兰妮。
- "What's the Story"… - "Work Bitch." Britney.
-“我在美国很无聊。”冲突。
- "I'm So Bored in the USA." The Clash.
-“我们必须离开这个地方。”
- "We're Gonna Have to Get Out of This Place."
-哦，在我的“小红帽”里？-“闭嘴开车。”
- Ooh, in my "Little Red Corvette"?
- "Shut Up and Drive."
-哦，“一起很糟糕。”
- Ooh, "Bad Together."
-“沉醉在爱中。”
- "Drunk in Love."
因为贝女王…-太棒了。-是 啊
Because Queen Bey is…
- Awesome.- Yeah.
-对不起，打断一下。
- Sorry to interrupt.
我能听到酸苹果的尖叫声吗？
Can I get a Sour Apple Scream?
对不起，
- Sorry, we were just…
在谈论歌曲标题。
- Talking in song titles.
“我喜欢这样。”
"I Like That."
珍妮尔·莫纳，是的。-Jan
elle Monáe.不错。
Janelle Monáe, yeah.- Janelle Monáe.Nice.
--好的，我休息。
- - All right, I'm on break.
-嗯，事实上，我们都摆脱了“酸苹果尖叫”。
- Uh, we're all out of Sour Apple Scream, actually.
它很受欢迎。
It's quite popular.
-菠萝惊喜？
- Pineapple Surprise?
-哦，这是我的最爱。
- Oh, it's my favorite.
我们以前见过吗？
Have we met before?
-不。
- Nah.
不，这是，呃…这是我第一次。
No, it's, uh… It's my first time.
-欢迎来到泥泞小屋。
- Welcome to the Slushy Shack.
我能帮你什么忙吗？
How may I help you?
-给我一分钟。
- Give me a minute.
我会想办法的。
I'll think of something.
嗯。
Mmm.
是的，所以高管培训计划旨在让像我这样的
候选人在日常特许经营方面有亲身体验。
Yeah, so the executive training program is, uh, designed
是的，所以高管培训计划旨在让像我这样的
候选人在日常特许经营方面有亲身体验。
to give candidates like me hands-on experience
是的，所以高管培训计划旨在让像我这样的
候选人在日常特许经营方面有亲身体验。
with day-to-day franchise operations.
-对-
- Right.-
嘿，雷金纳德。
Hey, Reginald.
第三份点心已经好了吗哦
Third snack already?- Oh.
休息一下，托德。
Give it a rest, Todd.
亲爱的上帝，
- Dear God,
或成熟的婴儿耶稣……
and/or grown-up baby Jesus…
无论我出生前支付了多少定金，
whatever down payment was made before I was born,
承诺了多少，
whatever was promised,
我都要退款。
I want a refund.
每一分钱，或者我都会向更好的商业局或教皇，可
能还有摩门教徒报告，如果他们被证明是相关的。
Every cent, or I will report you
每一分钱，或者我都会向更好的商业局或教皇，可
能还有摩门教徒报告，如果他们被证明是相关的。
to the Better Business Bureau
每一分钱，或者我都会向更好的商业局或教皇，可
能还有摩门教徒报告，如果他们被证明是相关的。
or the Pope
每一分钱，或者我都会向更好的商业局或教皇，可
能还有摩门教徒报告，如果他们被证明是相关的。
and possibly the Mormons,
每一分钱，或者我都会向更好的商业局或教皇，可
能还有摩门教徒报告，如果他们被证明是相关的。
if they turn out to be relevant.
我得到的承诺太多，以致于我没有得到。
I was promised so much that I did not receive.
市场营销具有欺骗性。
The marketing was deceptive.
当然，我可能并不确切地知道这一切是如何运作的…
…比如，什么样的生命被分配给了谁，为什么要这样
做，但我开始认为犯了一个明显不利于我的错误。
And, sure, I may not exactly know how it all works…
当然，我可能并不确切地知道这一切是如何运作的…
…比如，什么样的生命被分配给了谁，为什么要这样
做，但我开始认为犯了一个明显不利于我的错误。
Like, what life is handed out to who and why,
当然，我可能并不确切地知道这一切是如何运作的…
…比如，什么样的生命被分配给了谁，为什么要这样
做，但我开始认为犯了一个明显不利于我的错误。
but I'm beginning to think a mistake was made
当然，我可能并不确切地知道这一切是如何运作的…
…比如，什么样的生命被分配给了谁，为什么要这样
做，但我开始认为犯了一个明显不利于我的错误。
pretty obviously not in my favor.
因此，我并不满意。
And as a result, I'm not satisfied.
你知道吗？
And you know what?
除了退款外，
In addition to a refund,
我还想亲自道歉。
I'd like a personal apology.
我也希望夏天没有虫子，
I would also like bugless summers
汗腺也不那么活跃，
and less active sweat glands
在泥泞小屋外面找个人聊天。
and someone to talk to outside of the Slushy Shack.
而且，也许，只是一次，一次……幸运的休息。
And, like, maybe,
just one time, once…
而且，也许，只是一次，一次……幸运的休息。
a lucky break.
哇！
Whoa!
你把我吓得半死。
You scared me half to death.
你从哪里来？
Where did you even come from?
我甚至没听见你来。
I didn't even hear you coming.
-你叫什么名字？
- What's your name?
-雷金纳德·安德烈斯。
- Reginald Andres.
-叫我莫里斯。
- Call me Maurice.
-你好，莫里斯。
- Hi, Maurice.
你知道，我曾经读到，自我引导的谈话是一种健康的本能。
You know, I read once that self-directed talk
is a healthy instinct.
它有助于激励、指导和评估行动。
It assists in stimulating,
directing, and evaluating actions.
-我…我要的是我没有的东西。
- I… I was asking for things that I don't have.
-是的，就像祈祷一样。
- Yeah, like a prayer.
-实际上，我是无神论者。
- I'm an atheist, actually.
-我没有。
- I'm not.
-你听到了多少？
- How much did you hear?
我相信每个人都应该得到退款，
- I believe everyone deserves a refund,
有人可以交谈，
someone to talk to,
也有无障碍的夏天。
bugless summers, too.
-关闭时间。抓起拖把！
- Closing time.Grab a mop!
-你真的很喜欢她，是吗？
- You really like her, don't you?
-她叫莎拉。
- Her name is Sarah.
-也许你应该做点什么。
- Maybe you should do something about that.
约她出去。
Ask her out.
带她去吃晚饭和看电影。
Take her to dinner and a movie.
-有趣。你知道，你喜欢托德。
- Funny.You know, you'd like Todd.
他也有同样的笑话。
He has the same kind of jokes.
-你害怕了。
- You're afraid.
-与大多数男人不同，我知道自己的局限性。
- Unlike most men, I know my limitations.
-真相，雷吉？
- Truth, Reggie?
每个人都可以写自己的故事。
Everybody gets to write their own story.
好吧，
- Okay, I like a good fortune cookie
我和下一个人一样喜欢好运饼干，
as much as the next guy, but…
听我说。
- Listen to me.
回到那里去。
Go back in there.
不要害怕。
Do not be afraid.
问萨拉周五晚上是否有计划，
Ask Sarah if she has plans Friday night,
因为如果她没有，
because if she doesn't,
你认为你们两个出去会很有趣。
you think it'd be fun if the two of you went out.
也许去吃晚饭和看电影。
Maybe to dinner and a movie.
如果她说不，那没关系。
If she says no, that's okay.
只要说，“酷。也许下次吧。”
Just say, "Cool.Maybe next time."
但如果她答应了，你会笑得像你说的那样，对你的好运
感到很舒服，然后你会说：“很好，周五。你和我。”
But if she says yes,
但如果她答应了，你会笑得像你说的那样，对你的好运
感到很舒服，然后你会说：“很好，周五。你和我。”
you smile like you mean it,
但如果她答应了，你会笑得像你说的那样，对你的好运
感到很舒服，然后你会说：“很好，周五。你和我。”
totally comfortable with your good luck,
但如果她答应了，你会笑得像你说的那样，对你的好运
感到很舒服，然后你会说：“很好，周五。你和我。”
and you say, "Great.Friday.You and me."
“你和我”是承诺，而不是描述。
"You and me" is a promise, not a description.
你需要把这件事告诉她。
You need to communicate that to her.
然后你走开了，
And then you walk away,
就像你做了一件你应该做的事。
like you just did the one thing you were always meant to do.
祝你好运，孩子。
Good luck, kid.
-时间差不多了。
- About time.
-嘿，莎拉。-嘿
- Hey, Sarah.- Hey.
-星期五晚上你忙吗？
- Are you busy Friday night?
-呃，星期五？
- Uh, Friday?
不，不，我不忙。
No.No, I'm not busy.
-我想如果我们出去会很有趣。
- I think it would be fun if we went out.
也许是晚餐和电影。
Maybe dinner and a movie.
-当然可以。一、 ..我很乐意。
- Sure.I… I would like that.
-很好。星期五。
- Great.Friday.
你和我。
You and me.
-周六晚上你忙吗？
- You busy Saturday night?
因为我认为如果……-没有机会，托德，那会更有趣。
'Cause I think it'd be even more fun if…
- Not a chance, Todd.
-酷。完全理解。
- Cool.Completely understand.
对
Yes!
啊！
Ah!
哦！
Ooh!
如果你总是做你一直做的事，
- If you always do what you've always done,
你就会得到你一直得到的。
you'll always get what you've always got.
如果你总是做你一直做的事，
If you always do what you've always done,
你就会得到你一直得到的。
you'll always get what you've always got.
如果你总是做你一直做的事，
If you always do what you've always done,
你就会得到你一直得到的。
you'll always get what you've always got.
我希望你能再次出现。
I was hoping you'd show up again.
-嘿，Reggie。怎么了？
- Hey, Reggie.What's up?
-我们现在需要进行一次非常严肃的谈话。
- We need to have a very serious talk right now.
-怎么样？
- How's that?
-我明天和莎拉·金尼有个约会。
- I have a date with Sarah Kinney tomorrow.
这是一个积极的发展。
Well, that's a positive development.
你约她出去，她答应了。
You asked her out, and she said yes.
-这是我不明白的事情。
- That's the thing I don't understand.
-她说是吗？
- That she said yes?
就像我在那里，
- It's like I was there,
而不是在同一时间。
and not there at the same time.
就像，在我对这一刻的感知和这
一刻本身之间有一道物理障碍。
Like, there was a physical barrier
就像，在我对这一刻的感知和这
一刻本身之间有一道物理障碍。
between my perception of the moment
就像，在我对这一刻的感知和这
一刻本身之间有一道物理障碍。
and the moment itself.
就像我是雷金纳德而不是雷金纳德一样。
Like I was Reginald and not Reginald
at the same time.
-好的，好的。是的。
- Okay, okay.Yeah.
你可能想得太多了。
You might be overthinking things.
这只是晚餐和电影。
It's just dinner and a movie.
-在正常情况下，这没什么大不了的，对吧？
- Which, under normal circumstances,
is no big deal, right?
但鉴于我从未约会过，这是一件大事！
But seeing as how I've never been on a date,
it's a very big deal!
-等等。
- Hang on.
一次都没有？
Not even once?
好吧，好吧。
Okay, okay.
莎拉住在哪里？
Uh, where does Sarah live?
-嗯，木兰花和40号？
- Uh, Magnolia and 40th?
-好吧，嗯，在约会前一小时在圣弗兰克斯见我。
- All right, um, meet me at Saint Franks
an hour before your date.
-你认为一个小时的时间足以让我做好准备吗？
- Do you think an hour's long enough to prepare me?
一、 …我的意思是，我是一个快速学习的人，当然，但
是，我是说，我们谈论的是一个我没有经验的竞技场。
I… I mean, I'm a quick study, sure,
一、 …我的意思是，我是一个快速学习的人，当然，但
是，我是说，我们谈论的是一个我没有经验的竞技场。
but, I mean, we're talking about an arena
一、 …我的意思是，我是一个快速学习的人，当然，但
是，我是说，我们谈论的是一个我没有经验的竞技场。
in which I have zero experience.
-嘿，你相信我吗？
- Hey, do you trust me?
-完全正确，但我不知道为什么。
- Completely, but I have no idea why.
-我会告诉你该做什么，每一步，然后你就去做。
- I'll tell you what to do,
every step, and then you'll do it.
我现在有点泥泞了。
I'ma get a slushy now.
-酷。
- Cool.
酷，酷，酷。是的。
Cool, cool, cool.Yeah.
-你是个帅哥。我是说，告诉我，
- You're a good-looking guy.I mean, tell me,
你怎么从来没有约会过？
how have you never been on a date before?
-你现在是认真的吗？
- Are you serious right now?
-好吧，我明白了。你是个大块头，但是…
- All right, I get it.You're a big guy, but…
-大小很重要。
- Size matters.
-这很有趣。
- That's pretty funny.
-确实如此。我是说，我从来没有
- It does.I mean, I've never really had
有机会提高我的约会技巧，
the chance to work on my dating skills
因为我从来没有真正的约会。
'cause I never really had dates.
孤独是我的自然栖息地。
And loneliness was sort of my natural habitat.
而且女孩们并没有被像我这样的男人所吸引。
And girls aren't exactly…
attracted to guys like me.
-也许他们不认识真正的你。
- Maybe they don't know the real you.
-感觉他们有一个很好的主意。
- It feels like they have
a pretty good idea.
-嘿，离你第一次约会还有47分钟。
- Hey, 47 minutes till your first date.
-是的，我还需要十个。
- Yeah, I'm gonna need about ten more of these.
-听着。
- Listen.
倒霉。
Shit.
-如你所愿。
- As you wish.
-不，不，不。不是你，雷吉。
- No, no, no.Not you, Reggie.
-他们是你的朋友吗一点也没有。
- Are they friends of yours?- Not even a little bit.
听着，我需要尽快处理这件事。
Look, I need to handle this real quick.
这不会花很长时间。
It shouldn't take long.
-离我第一次约会还有46分钟。
- 46 minutes till my first date.
-在时钟上。知道了。
- On the clock.Got it.
-它们看起来不错。
- They seem nice.
-你叫什么名字？
- What's your name?
-关于…雷金纳德·安德烈斯。
- Re… Reginald Andres.
-很高兴见到你，雷金纳德。
- Nice to meet you, Reginald.
我是莫伊拉。
I'm Moira.
-莫伊拉，别再胡扯了。
- Moira, stop that shit, now.
-他是你的吗？
- Is he yours?
雷吉，
- Reggie, meet Moira, Penelope,
勒布朗和艾萨克。
LeBron, and Isaac.
他们需要我几分钟的时间。
They need a couple minutes of my time.
-哦，我想不止一对。
- Oh, more than a couple, I think.
-莫里斯一直很坏。
- Maurice has been bad.
-勒布朗和艾萨克需要和我在后面聊天。
- LeBron and Isaac need to chat with me out back.
你觉得怎么样，雷吉？
How's that sound with you, Reggie?
-我…我马上就来。
- I… I'll be right here.
-莫伊拉和佩内洛普将留在这里。
- Moira and Penelope will remain here.
-哦，那……这对我来说不是问题。
- Oh, that's… that's not a problem for me.
-雷吉，你最好跟我们一起去。
- Reggie, it's best if you come with us.
-好的。
- Okay.
-我会想念你的。
- I'll miss you.
-雷吉，我们走吧。
- Reggie, let's go.
-莫里斯·米勒，你的挑衅，你的无礼，看。
- Maurice Miller, for your defiance,
for your impertinence, look.
--看。
- - Look.
-把那狗屎弄出去。
- Get that shit outta here.
-雷吉·雷金纳德。
- Reggie.Reginald.
雷吉·雷金纳德·雷金纳多。
Reggie.Reginald.Reginaldo.
-Bonsoir，ma petit bouchee。
- Bonsoir, ma petit bouchée.
-你闻起来很香。
- You smell amazing.
-你想成为我们的吗？
- Do you wanna be ours?
-我们很高兴与大家分享。
- We're happy to share.
-你说分享是什么意思？
- When you say share, what do you mean?
-别管他！
- Leave him alone!
-该死，Reggie。
- Damn it, Reggie.
走开！
Go away!
-也许只是在我们离开之前品尝一下。
- Maybe just a taste before we depart.
-怎么…你怎么…-匹克的木头。
- How… how did you…
- Pick's wooden.
-你觉得你能告诉莎拉我约会要迟到了吗？
- Do you think you can tell Sarah
I'm gonna be late for the date?
你可以用我的手机。
You can use my cell.
-不，我能解决这个问题，Reggie。
- No, I can fix this, Reggie.
好吧，但是我……没有你的同意我做不到。
Okay, but I… I can't do it without your say-so.
决定权在你。
The decision has to be yours.
-决定？
- Decide?
-没错。
- That's right.
决定现在就死，提前几分钟。
Decide to die now, a few moments early.
-我为什么要这样做？
- Why would I do that?
-所以我可以救你。
- So I can save you.
-好的。-可以
- Okay.- Okay.
-好的。好的。
- Okay.Okay.
我昨晚做了一个最奇怪的梦。
I had the weirdest dream last night.
-不，你不是在做梦正当
- No, you're not dreaming.- Right.
对，对。
Right, right.
我明白了。我知道这里发生了什么。
I get it.I know what's happening here.
我还在做梦。
I'm still dreaming.
就像，这是我醒来的第一个梦，现在我
在做第二个梦，就像是续集，对吧？
Like, this is the first dream I woke up from,
就像，这是我醒来的第一个梦，现在我
在做第二个梦，就像是续集，对吧？
and now I'm in the second one, like it's a sequel, right?
-不，这不是续集。
- Nah, it's not a sequel.
-你当然会这么说。你是一个投影
- Of course you'd say that.You're a projection
我的潜意识。
of my unconscious mind.
哇，等一下。
Whoa, wait a minute.
我不是在做梦。
I'm not dreaming.
我在做清醒梦。
I'm lucid dreaming.
这不可能是我的血。
This can't be my blood.
我会死的。-是的，你会的。
I'd be dead.- Yeah, you would be.
-你把我带到这里来了。-不能呆在酒吧里。
- You brought me here.- Couldn't stay at the bar.
警察已经上路了。
Cops were on their way.
-我不是在做梦吧？
- I'm not dreaming, am I?
-编号。
- No.
圣弗兰克斯。
Saint Franks.
在小巷里。
In the alley.
莫伊拉，佩内洛普，勒布朗，艾萨克。
Moira, Penelope, LeBron, Isaac.
我的意思是，艾萨克现在已经是灰烬了，但是……当我
在处理这件事的时候，莫伊拉和佩内洛普找到了你。
I mean, Isaac is ashes now, but…
我的意思是，艾萨克现在已经是灰烬了，但是……当我
在处理这件事的时候，莫伊拉和佩内洛普找到了你。
while I was dealing with that, Moira and Penelope got to you.
听着，雷吉，你会死的，伙计。
Look, Reggie,
you were gonna die, man.
我问你想不想活下去，
I asked you if you wanted to live and you said…
好的。
- Okay.
哦。
Ooh.
但他们想从你那里得到什么？
But what did they want from you?
-一位区域主任向他们发送了一份投诉清单。
- A Regional Director sent them with a list of complaints.
可能的制裁。
Possible sanctions.
-你是……销售人员吗？
- Are… are you in sales?
-雷吉，你知道我是什么，伙计。
- Reggie, you know what I am, man.
-但他们想从我这里得到什么？
- But what did they want from me?
-莫伊拉和佩内洛普喜欢玩他们的食物。
- Moira and Penelope like to play with their food.
-哦，不。
- Oh, no.
不
No.
吸血鬼不是真的。
Vampires are not real.
他们只是一个故事看
They're just a story.- Look,
你是个母亲…吸血鬼，伙计。
you're a mother… vampire, man.
你是不死族。
You're undead.
你永远不会死。
You can never die.
永远不要变老。
Never grow old.
我的意思是，除非有人把你押在心上，或者你被困在阳
光下，否则你不会死，但这是非常、非常不可能的。
I mean, you can't die
我的意思是，除非有人把你押在心上，或者你被困在阳
光下，否则你不会死，但这是非常、非常不可能的。
unless someone stakes you in the heart
我的意思是，除非有人把你押在心上，或者你被困在阳
光下，否则你不会死，但这是非常、非常不可能的。
or you get stranded in the sun, but that's very, very unlikely.
-我还能吃披萨吗？
- Can I still eat pizza?
-是的，努力吧。你可以吃披萨。
- Yeah, go for it.You can eat pizza.
-冰淇淋怎么样？-冰淇淋也是。
- What about ice cream?- Ice cream, too.
-所以我的味蕾还在品尝？
- So my taste buds still taste?
-我认为你现在有点过分强调披萨和冰淇淋了。
- I think you're putting a little too much emphasis
on the pizza and the ice cream right now.
-但如果我的消化系统像以前那样
工作…-你的味蕾仍然有味道。
- But if my digestive system works the way it did before…
-但如果我的消化系统像以前那样
工作…-你的味蕾仍然有味道。
- Your taste buds still taste.
但他们最想尝的是血。
But what they wanna taste most of all is blood.
它是唯一滋养你的东西。
It's the only thing that nourishes you.
-每天？
- Every day?
-不，你的身体会告诉你它需要什么。
- No, your body will tell you what it needs.
-我是一个母亲…吸血鬼。
- I'm a mother… vampire.
-是的-
- Yes.-
-是的，这就是精神。
- Yes, that's the spirit.
-亡灵。-彻底地
- Undead.- Completely.
-我永远不会变老。
- I will never age and never grow old.
-好吧，现在你只是重复我说的话。
- All right, now you're just repeating what I said.
-超高速。吸血鬼有这个，对吗？
- Superspeed.Vampires have that, right?
-是的，我的意思是，有些情况下，
但它…-我是一个母亲…吸血鬼。
- Yeah, I mean, some cases, but it…
-是的，我的意思是，有些情况下，
但它…-我是一个母亲…吸血鬼。
- I'm a mother… vampire.
-我们得讨论一下这个口号。
- We're gonna have to workshop that catchphrase.
-超高速！
- Superspeed!
哇！
Whoo!
我是一个母亲…吸血鬼…-别再这
样了，伙计。-是的，没什么。
I'm a mother… vamp…
我是一个母亲…吸血鬼…-别再这
样了，伙计。-是的，没什么。
- Do not try that again, man.- Yeah, no shit.
我为什么在呼吸？我为什么出汗？
Why am I breathing?Why am I sweating?
我应该已经死了。
I'm supposed to be dead.
-嗯，让我们成为吸血鬼的东西
，它改变了每个系统的功能。
- Well, the thing that makes us vampires,
-嗯，让我们成为吸血鬼的东西
，它改变了每个系统的功能。
it alters the functions of every system.
好吧，这就是我们能这么快愈合的原因。
All right, that's how we can heal so fast.
但我们的器官，它们仍然起着同样的作用。
But our organs, they still work the same.
这基本上只是你本质的加速。
It's basically just an acceleration
of your essential nature.
好吧，我以前跑得很快。
Okay, I was fast before.
现在我快了。
Now I'm, like, fast-fast.
我以前很强壮，现在我变得非常强壮。
And I was strongish, and now I'm crazy strong.
你明白了。-等待
You get it.- Wait.
你说的是超快速治疗吗？
Did you say superfast healing?
我有，所以很酷。
I have that, so that's cool.
是的，
- Yeah, that's cool, but, um…
这很酷，
look, the, uh…
但是，
the enhancements of every vampire
看，
are relative to the condition they're in
每个吸血鬼的增强效果都与他们改变时的状态有关。
at the time of their change.
因为他们死去的身体…是他们永远拥有的身体。
Because the body they die with…
is the body they'll have forever.
-哇，等等。
- Whoa, wait.
什么
What?
我永远都是这样，
I'm like this forever,
我对此无能为力，
and I can't do anything about it,
你直到现在才说什么？
and you didn't say anything until now?
-是的。
- Yeah.
节食不是一种选择。
Dieting isn't an option.
-但那是真的吗？
- But was it ever?
-你知道我的意思。
- You know what I mean.
-不要节食，好吧，但是看，我们还有其他问题，好吗？
- No dieting, all right, but look,
we got other problems, okay?
根据你的形状和大小…-你可以说“胖”
Given your shape and size…
- You can say "fat."
我不怕这个词。
I'm not afraid of the word.
-好吧，胖子。是的。
- Okay, fat.Yeah.
作为一个胖吸血鬼，这会给吸血鬼社区带来一些问题。
Being a fat vampire,
that's gonna cause some problems
作为一个胖吸血鬼，这会给吸血鬼社区带来一些问题。
within the vampire community.
-哦，就像我在停车场遇到你的朋友一样？
- Oh, like with your friends that I met in the parking lot?
-是的。
- Yeah.
是的，他们死前都是混蛋。
Yeah, they were assholes before they died.
虚荣、固执、肥胖、羞耻的欺负者。
Vain, bigoted, fat-shaming bullies.
-我对这种态度并不陌生。
- I'm not unfamiliar with the attitude.
-好的。好的。
- Okay.Okay.
那么你就明白为什么我们要保持低调，
So then you understand why we gotta keep this all low-key
直到我能找出后果。
until I can figure out the consequences.
-你是说我在吸血鬼社区可能不受欢迎吗？
- Are you saying that I may not be welcome
in the vampire community?
他们对我构成威胁？
That they pose a threat to me?
有些事情永远不会改变。
Some things never change.
我会永远这样。
I'm gonna be like this forever.
如果你总是做你一直做的事，
If you always do what you've always done,
你就会得到你一直得到的。
you'll always get what you've always got.
-真是一口。
- That's a mouthful.
-亨利·福特说过。
- Henry Ford said it.
-是吗？
- Yeah?
嗯，亨利·福特认为犹太人发明爵士乐
是为了腐败美国，所以……-说得对。
Well, Henry Ford believed
嗯，亨利·福特认为犹太人发明爵士乐
是为了腐败美国，所以……-说得对。
Jews invented jazz to corrupt America, so…
嗯，亨利·福特认为犹太人发明爵士乐
是为了腐败美国，所以……-说得对。
- Point taken.
-太阳来了。
- Sun's coming.
该回家了。
Time to go home.
-我没事。
- I'm okay.
我没事。
I'm okay.
噢
Ow.
说来话长…-那么，雷金纳德，重要的约会怎么样？
Long story…
- So, Reginald, how was the big date?
-莎拉今晚上晚班，对吗？
- Sarah's got the late shift tonight, right?
-晚餐和电影。
- Dinner and a movie.
这就是交易，对吧？
That was the deal, right?
你和…莎拉。
You and…
Sarah.
天啊，你知道我搞不懂的是，她为什么会把
时间浪费在像你这样明显的失败者身上？
God, you know what I can't figure out is
天啊，你知道我搞不懂的是，她为什么会把
时间浪费在像你这样明显的失败者身上？
why would she waste her time on an obvious loser like you?
我的意思是，
I mean, unless this is like
除非这是一个令人遗憾的聚会。
one of those Make-A-Wish pity parties.
或者萨拉只是一个像你一样的失败者。
Or maybe Sarah's just a loser like you.
-不要让你说出她的名字。
- Keep her name out of your mouth.
我不在乎你怎么看我，
I don't care what you think about me,
别紧张，
but if you ever talk shit about Sarah again…
Reg。
- Take it easy, Reg.
只是开玩笑而已。
Just kidding around.
不是故意的。
Didn't mean any of it.
怪胎
Freak!
嗯。
Mmm.
嗯，嗯-哦，天哪。
Mmm, mmm.- Oh, my.
我在这里看到了什么-
What am I seeing here?-
-暴饮暴食症，也称为BED，是一种威胁生命
的疾病，通常伴有使人虚弱的内疚感和羞耻感。
- Binge eating disorder, also known as BED,
-暴饮暴食症，也称为BED，是一种威胁生命
的疾病，通常伴有使人虚弱的内疚感和羞耻感。
is a life-threatening condition usually accompanied
-暴饮暴食症，也称为BED，是一种威胁生命
的疾病，通常伴有使人虚弱的内疚感和羞耻感。
by debilitating guilt and shame.
好消息是有有效的治疗方法，
The good news is that there are effective treatments,
从心理治疗开始。
starting with psychotherapy.
-我姑妈乔伊斯得了床。
- My Aunt Joyce
suffered from BED.
治疗帮助她解决了导致她的疾病的
生理、生物、人际和文化因素。
Therapy helped her to address the physical, biological,
治疗帮助她解决了导致她的疾病的
生理、生物、人际和文化因素。
interpersonal, and cultural forces
治疗帮助她解决了导致她的疾病的
生理、生物、人际和文化因素。
attributing to her condition.
我会告诉你她的治疗师的名字。
I'm gonna give you the name of her therapist.
现在，保险业将成为一场噩梦，很遗憾你不住在荷兰。
Now, insurance is going to be a nightmare,
and too bad you don't live in the Netherlands.
但重要的是你得到了帮助…雷金纳德？
But the important thing is
that you get the help that you…
但重要的是你得到了帮助…雷金纳德？
Reginald?
-那么，从一到“什么……”，好日子还是坏日子？
- So on a scale of one to "what the…,"
good or bad day?
-看起来我今天过得好吗？
- Does it look like I'm having a good day right now?
-好吧，希望之泉…-永恒？
- Well, hope springs… - Eternal?
我明白了。
I get it.
就像永恒的饥饿燃烧着我的内心。
Like the eternal hunger burning me inside.
我看人的时候不能不看到他们的血管或闻到他们的血液。
I can't look at people without seeing their veins
or smelling their blood.
-嗯，它们是食物。-它们不是我的食物。
- Well, they're food.- They are not food to me.
-你为什么认为今晚上班是个好主意？
- What made you think coming into work tonight
was a good idea?
我错过了与莎拉的约会，
- I missed my date with Sarah because I was being turned
因为我被变成了当晚的不死生物。
into an undead creature of the night.
我想说对不起你需要吃东西，伙计。
I wanted to say I'm sorry.- You need to feed, man.
否则你看到的每个人都会像个该死的血袋子。
Or else everyone you see
is gonna look like a damn blood bag.
你明白我的意思吗？
You understand me?
-但我不想杀任何人。
- But I don't wanna kill anyone.
-你不必这么做。
- You don't have to.
好吧喝你需要的。
All right?Drink what you need.
让他们忘记你喝酒了。
Make them forget you drank.
只是美化一下自己的晚餐。
Just glamour yourself some dinner.
听我说。
Listen to me.
-对不起，我没有感觉到-
- Sorry, not feeling it.-
伙计，这只是为了演示。
Dude, this was just for demonstration purposes.
吸血鬼不能吸引其他吸血鬼，好吗？
Vampires can't glamour other vampires, all right?
现在你试试看。
Now you try.
-听我说。
- Listen to me.
-不。
- Nah.
不，你必须更深入。
No, you gotta lean into it more.
说得像你说的那样。
Say it like you mean it.
-听我说。-嗯。
- Listen to me.- Mm.
给你。
There you go.
听着，你明白了，伙计。
Look, you got this, man.
只要敲一下你的大脑袋。
Just tap into that big brain of yours.
-你怎么知道我有一个大脑袋？
- How do you know I have a big brain?
-伙计，我是你的创造者。
- Dude, I'm your maker.
我知道你的一切。
I know everything about you.
还有一件事。
One more thing.
除非你喂食，
Until you feed,
否则你认识的每个人都有风险。
everyone you know is at risk.
莎拉有危险，
Sarah is at risk,
我知道你不想那样。
and I know you don't want that.
-我宁愿踏入阳光。
- I'd rather step into the sun.
-所以你欠她的不仅仅是道歉。
- So you owe her more than an apology.
我们都知道。
We both know it.
-你怎么了？
- What happened to you?
我以为你今晚在工作。
I thought you were working tonight.
-我们需要分手。
- We need to break up.
-我不知道我们在一起。
- I didn't know we were together.
我是说，
- I mean,
我们不能再见面了。
we can't see each other anymore.
-不过，我们从未见过面。
- We never did see each other, though.
-我不想再和你约会了。
- I don't wanna go on a date with you anymore.
首先问你是个错误。
And it was a mistake to ask you in the first place.
-好的。
- Okay.
当然。随便。
Sure.Whatever.
-我没看就知道是你。
- I knew it was you without even looking.
-我是你的创造者，伙计。
- I'm your maker, man.
我们共享鲜血。
We share blood.
这是一个强大的连接。
That's a powerful connection.
听着，
Look, wherever you are…
我知道你在哪里。
I know where you are.
不管你感觉如何，我也感觉到了，雷吉。
Whatever you're feeling,
I feel it too, Reggie.
-我妈妈和爸爸搬到了夏威夷。
- My mom and dad moved to Hawaii.
他们喜欢太阳。
They love the sun.
我再也见不到他们了，是吗？
I'm never gonna see them again, am I?
-可能不会。
- Probably not.
-你见过你的父母吗？
- Did you ever see your parents?
-是的。
- Yeah.
就一次。
Just once.
-我妈妈就是这种自然力。
- My mom's this force of nature.
她是我获得工商管理理学学士学位的原因。
She's the reason I got my bachelor of science degree
in business administration.
她认为它可以为我打开任何一扇门。
She thought it could open any door for me.
只是……
And the Slushy Shack was just…
本该是一篇学期论文的研究。
Was just supposed to be research for a term paper.
两年后，我仍然在这里。
Two years later, I'm still here.
-但你留下了，嗯？
- But you stayed, huh?
-学生贷款是贷款中的不死贷款。
- Student loans are the undead loans of loans.
它们是永恒的。
They're eternal.
-是的。
- Yeah.
-我不太喜欢我的生活。
- I didn't like my life much.
这在很多方面都有问题，但……我想我
会怀念它，我不认为那种感觉会消失。
It was problematic in a lot of ways, but…
这在很多方面都有问题，但……我想我
会怀念它，我不认为那种感觉会消失。
I think I'm gonna miss it, and I don't think
这在很多方面都有问题，但……我想我
会怀念它，我不认为那种感觉会消失。
that feeling's ever gonna go away.
-会的，雷吉。
- It will, Reggie.
相信我。
Trust me.
总有一天，你的旧生活，看起来
就像……就像你做过的一个梦。
One day, your old life, it's just gonna seem like…
总有一天，你的旧生活，看起来
就像……就像你做过的一个梦。
Like a dream you had.
其中一个是清醒的。
One of those lucid ones.
-你100%肯定吗？
- Are you 100% sure about that?
-是的。
- Yeah.
100%.- 听着，很多孩子在我
们开始这个项目之前从未吃过早餐。
100%.
100%.- 听着，很多孩子在我
们开始这个项目之前从未吃过早餐。
- Look, a lot of these kids never had breakfast
100%.- 听着，很多孩子在我
们开始这个项目之前从未吃过早餐。
before we started the program.
附近的每一个杂货店都捐赠。
Every grocer in the neighborhood donates.
你需要捐款。
You need to donate.
-安吉拉。-是的，让我给你回电话。
- Angela.- Yeah, let me call you back.
发生了什么事，年轻的士兵？
What happened there, young soldier?
-孩子们拧开消防栓，在水里玩耍。
- Kids wrenched open a hydrant, playing in the water.
警察无缘无故地殴打他们。
Cop roughed 'em up for no good reason at all.
我想我对此很反感。
Guess I took exception to that.
-看起来很像。
- Looks like it.
-是的。
- Yeah.
是的，我得到的是一根错误的警棍。
Yeah, wrong end of a nightstick, what I get.
-你和我今晚为什么不出去？
- Why don't you and I go out tonight?
谈谈你得到了什么。
Talk about what it is that you get.
-嘿，那些是什么，呃…我们喝的鸡尾酒？
- Hey, what were those, uh… The cocktails we had?
-麦泰斯-是的，是的。
- Mai tais.- Yeah, yeah.
是的，他们有很酷的小雨伞。
Yeah, they got cool little umbrellas.
莫里斯，
What is it that you want, Maurice,
你到底想要什么？
out there in the world?
你想要什么？
What is it that you want?
-正义。
- Justice.
-你觉得怎么样？
- And how's that going for you?
-嗯，你觉得怎么样？
- Well, how do you think?
-如果我告诉你还有另一种战斗方式呢？
- What if I told you there was another way to fight?
打破那些母亲的方式…-我想让你确切地告诉我是什么。
A way to break those mother…
- I'd want you to tell me exactly what it was.
然后我会把它们打碎。
And then I'd break 'em.
这是一种改变，莫里斯。
It's a change, Maurice.
我可以为你做到这一点。
And I can do that for you.
如果你允许的话。
If you give me your permission.
-这是你做的改变吗？
- Is this change something you did?
-是的。
- It is.
-你什么时候做的？
- And when'd you do that?
嗯？
Huh?
-让我们说这不是我的第一次革命。
- Let's just say
this isn't my first revolution.
-等等，什么？
- Wait, what?
安吉。
Angie.
-听着，安吉，如果你只想做爱
，你不需要告诉我一些故事。
- Look, Angie, you didn't need to tell me some story
-听着，安吉，如果你只想做爱
，你不需要告诉我一些故事。
if all you wanted was sex.
-莫里斯，我不是在要求性爱。
- I'm not asking for sex, Maurice.
嗯，
- Well, I'm getting some seriously mixed vibes
我现在有一些严重混合的感觉你想打架吗？
right now.- Do you want to fight?
-我是这么说的。很明显。
- I said that.Clearly.
-你允许我吗？
- Do I have your permission?
-听着，做你该做的，但我想你
对这里发生的事情感到困惑。
- Look, do what you gotta do, but I think you're confused
-听着，做你该做的，但我想你
对这里发生的事情感到困惑。
what's happening here.
你允许我吗？
Do I have your permission?
啊哈。
Ahh.
我想我更喜欢你的起源故事，
- I think I like your origin story
而不是我的起源故事。
better than my origin story.
安吉拉怎么了？
What happened to Angela?
-我不想谈论安吉拉。
- I don't wanna talk about Angela.
-她教过你怎么这样生活吗？
- Did she teach you how to live like this?
-不。
- Nah.
不，我必须自己学。
No, I had to learn that on my own.
-这是规则吗？
- Is that a rule?
-为什么？-嗯，我希望
- Why?- Well, I'm hoping
你会教我的。
you'll teach me.
-是的。
- Yeah.
我能做到。
I can do that.
-我也希望你能成为我的朋友。
- I'm also hoping you'll be my friend.
-听着，雷吉，我有关于朋友的规定。
- Look, Reggie, I got rules about friends.
迟早，你知道…-拜托。
Sooner or later, you know… - Please.
是 啊是的，我也能做到。
Yeah.Yeah, I can do that, too.
那晚在泥泞小屋后面……
- That night behind the Slushy Shack…
你打算吃我吗？
were you going to feed on me?
-是的。
- Yup.
-你为什么没有？
- Why didn't you?
-我不知道，伙计。
- I don't know, man.
我想我是一个……一个真正的浪漫主义者。
I guess I'm a… A sucker for true romance.
-我们昨晚应该告诉她。
- We should have told her last night.
她不会高兴的。
She will not be pleased.
-这不是我们的错。
- It's not our fault.
-莫里斯杀了艾萨克。
- Maurice killed Isaac.
-砍掉他的头。
- Off with his head.
-她会理解的。
- She will understand.
她会让他受苦的。
And she will make him suffer.
我们按你的要求召见了莫里斯。
We summoned Maurice, as you requested.
-但他无视你的命令。
- But he ignored your command.
-所以我吃了他的同伴。
- So I ate his companion.
-莫里斯杀了艾萨克。-艾萨克是个大人物。
- Maurice killed Isaac.- Isaac is very much dust.
-他的同伴尝到了康沃尔馅饼。
- His companion tasted of Cornish pasty.
-你吃了他的同伴？
- You ate his companion?
-我饿了。
- I was hungry.
-嗯，你把尸体处理掉了吗？
- Well, did you dispose of the body?
-莫里斯把我们赶走了。
- Maurice chased us away.
没有时间了。
There was no time.
-所以你只是留下了你渴望别人找到的证据。
- So you just left evidence of your hunger
for others to find.
-我不怕活着的男人或女人。
- I fear no living man or woman.
-你害怕我吗？
- Do you fear me?
-司法公正。
- Justice dispensed.
-正义应得。
- Justice deserved.
-饶了我们吧。-请
- Spare us.- Please.
-请。
- Please.
告诉我莫里斯的同伴。
Tell me about Maurice's companion.
第44页“格莱美奖后的胜利，
Page 44."Post-Grammy win,
梅根·赛义·史马利昂正在开创一个新的世界。”
a new world is opening up for Megan Thee Stallion."
哦
Oh.
第62页。
Page 62.
到1979年底，
"By late 1979, Prince and the Revolution
王子与革命开始上演他们的第一场俱乐部演出。
start to play their first club showcases."
第377页。
Page 377.
莫里斯。
Maurice.
你不会相信我能做什么。
You won't believe what I can do.
-你好。
- Hi.
这可能会让你大吃一惊，可能会妨碍你和
我分手的计划，尽管我们从未在一起。
This may come as a surprise to you,
这可能会让你大吃一惊，可能会妨碍你和
我分手的计划，尽管我们从未在一起。
and it probably interferes with your plan
这可能会让你大吃一惊，可能会妨碍你和
我分手的计划，尽管我们从未在一起。
to break up with me,
这可能会让你大吃一惊，可能会妨碍你和
我分手的计划，尽管我们从未在一起。
even though we were never together.
但我考虑了一下，我拒绝你想象中的分手，我认为你和我
需要就我们之间发生的事情进行一次公开和诚实的对话。
But I gave it some thought,
但我考虑了一下，我拒绝你想象中的分手，我认为你和我
需要就我们之间发生的事情进行一次公开和诚实的对话。
and I reject your imaginary breakup
但我考虑了一下，我拒绝你想象中的分手，我认为你和我
需要就我们之间发生的事情进行一次公开和诚实的对话。
and think that you and I need to have
但我考虑了一下，我拒绝你想象中的分手，我认为你和我
需要就我们之间发生的事情进行一次公开和诚实的对话。
an open and honest conversation
但我考虑了一下，我拒绝你想象中的分手，我认为你和我
需要就我们之间发生的事情进行一次公开和诚实的对话。
about what's going on between us.
因为我知道当你认为我没有看的时候你是怎么看我的。
Because I know how you look at me
when you think I'm not looking.
但你不知道的是，我有时是如何……看着你的。
But what you don't know is how I sometimes…
look at you.
-我现在可以进来吗？
- Can I come in now, please?
-好的。-可以
- Okay.- Okay.